Guide to the Cornell Center for Materials Research records, 1970-2008
Cornell Center for Materials Research records
- Series II. Reports
  - Subseries IIc: Material Science Center Technical Reports and Theses
    - MSC Reports- Microfilm Index (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - MSC Reports- #6901-7432, June 1992 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      Quarterly Reports
    - MSC Reports- #7164-7514, September 1992 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - MSC Technical Reports and Theses on microfilm- #1-5400, 62 reels, 1961-1984 (Box 40)
  - Subseries IId: Various Other Reports
    - Personnel Info., 1987, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - MSC Central Facility Review, 1970; 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Administrative Report, 1968-1971 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Steady State Level of the Operations of the Materials Science Center, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Administrative Reports, 1964-1967 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Administrative Reports, 1961-1963 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Fiscal Support / History of ARPA, 1960-1970 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Science and Technology Report; Center Directors' Meetings / Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Science and Government Report- Part I, 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Science and Government Report- Part II, 1975-1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Visiting Committee Report, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Efforts Reports, 1993-1996 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Efforts Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Biographical Report, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Equipment Reports, Facility Equipment List- Computing Facility, 1988, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Equipment Reports, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Equipment Reports, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Facilities Report, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Facilities Report, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Corning Pre-Buy Corresp.; Facility Managers' Report, 2006-2007 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - NYSTAR etc., 2007-2008 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Interdisciplinary Materials Research, 2005, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Special Reports, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Special Reports, 2003-2207 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - CCMR- Shared Experimental Facilities and Services Report, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Evaluative Study of the MRL Program- Summary Report, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - MRSEC- Reporting Requirements, 1989-1997 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Site Visit Report- MRL, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - NSF Final Project Report, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Clark Hall Safety Report, 1984, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Clark Hall Safety Committee, 1978-1989 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Impact of ARPA in Material Science- Report, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Research Project Descriptions, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Annual Reports to the Vice Presidents, 1987-1988, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Research Future Task Force Report, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Office VP for Research - Annual Report, 1999, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Convex Final Report, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Series III. Proposals
  - REM Prog. Ext, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Final Report 98A DMR-8703496, 1983-1986, 1986-1989, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - DMR 85-16616 AOI, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 12 Month Proposal to NSF, Final Report 98A DMR-8416040, 1985-1986, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Final Report 98A DMR 82-17227, Amendment #2 to NSF-Capital Equipment, 1987, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - DMR-8217227 AOI, DMR-8217227, 1984-1985, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Final Report 98A Dmr-7924008, 1980-1983 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - DMR-7924008 A03, AO4, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - DMR-7924008 AO2, AO1, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - DMR-7924008, Final Report 98A, 1980-1981, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - DMR 7681083, DMR 7601281, 1977-1979, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - DMR 7203029, 1972, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - 1995, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - K-12 Outreach Info, Budget Info (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Proposals Due- Capital Equipment, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Research Proposal-Corning, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - IRS Proposals/Correspondence- Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Keck Foundation Proposal, 1985,1989 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Proposal for MRSEC, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Research Proposal- MRL, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Research Proposal- MRL- Silcox, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Research Proposal- MRL- Silsbee, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Research Proposal- Microkelvin Research Laboratory, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Research Proposal- Materials Research Laboratory, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Proposal Response- Advanced Research Projects Agency, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - ARPA Proposal, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Final Report 98A, 1989-1992 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Proposal- NSF, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Proposal-NSF (Supplement), 1990 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Proposal DMR-8818558 AO2, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Proposal DMR-8818558, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Proposal- MSC, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - MSC Members' Individual Research Proposals (1st Half), 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - MSC Members' Individual Research Proposals (2nd Half), 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - IRG Renewal Proposals, Structural Proposals, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - DOE Proposals, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - IRG Proposals, IGERT Proposal, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - SEED Proposal, CCMR, IGERT Proposal, 2006,2007 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Research Proposal- Interdisciplinary Materials Research, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Research Proposal- Superconducting Quantum, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Research Proposal- Interdisciplinary Materials Research, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Research Proposal- Experimental Computer Control, Metallic Hydrogen Systems, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Proposal DMR8818558, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Proposal for a Materials Science Center, Apr 1960 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Research Proposal DMR9121654, Materials Research Laboratory, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Research Proposal DMR9121654, MRSEC-Silcox, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Research Proposal- Supplement to DMR9121645, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - MRSEC Proposal- With Correspondence, 1996-2001 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - MRSEC Prepoposal, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - MRSEC Proposal- Correspondence and Reviews, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - MRSEC Proposal- DMR9632275, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Research Proposal- Materials Research, Laboratory- Silsbee, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Research Proposal- Materials Research Science and ENGG Centers Program- Silcox, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Research Proposal- Materials Research Laboratory- Silcox, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Funding Request- 2nd year Continuing Grant, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Continuing Proposal Info., 1988-1993 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Supplemental NSF Proposals, Mar 1990, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Research Proposal- MRL Program, May 1985 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Research Proposal- MRL Program, July 1979 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - CMMR Prepoposal, 2004,2005 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Research Proposal- MRL Program (3rd year), 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Research Proposal- MRL Program (2nd year), 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Research Proposal- MRL Program (3rd year continuation), 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Research Proposal- MRL Program, July 1982 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Capital Equipment Proposal, 2000,2003 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - MRSEC Continuation Proposal, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Total Requests, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Research Proposal to ARPA, Nov 1973, Jun 1973-May 1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Renewal Proposal, Sept 1969, Dec 1970 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Renewal Proposal, Oct 1967, Nov 1968 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Renewal Proposal, Oct 1965, Oct 1966 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Renewal Proposal, Nov 1963, Nov 1964 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Renewal Proposal, Dec 1961, Nov 1962 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Renewal Proposal, Dec 1960 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Research Proposal to ARPA, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - MRSEC Prepoposal, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - MRSEC Proposal, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - MRSEC Materials Research Laboratory, 1992-1995 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - MRSEC Continuation Request- Part I, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - MRSEC Continuation Request- Part II, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Continuation Report DMR9121654, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - MRSEC Continuation Request, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - MRSEC Continuation Request, Mar-Aug 2000 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Proposal-MRSEC-CCMR, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Proposal-MRSEC-CCMR, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Proposal for MRSEC, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - MRSEC Proposal- CCMR, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Facilities, SEEDs, Memos, Format, Capital Equipment Needs, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - 1/2 New Pending, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - NSP-ISE-PRE-DiSalvo, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - MSC Members Proposal Budget Request, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Proposal-Sicox-Quantum Phenomena, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - MSC Project Proposal- Ceramics, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - MSC Project Proposal- Meterocycles, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - MSC Project Proposal- Polymer Composites, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - MSC Project Proposal- Surfaces and Interfaces, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - MSC Project Proposal- Theory/ Modelling, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - MSC Research Proposal- 3rd year (DMR8217227), 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Research Proposal- Continuation Grant, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Capital Equipment Proposals, 1982-1986 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Materials Research Proposal-Silcox, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - MSC Eexecutive Committee- Corresp. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - MSC Facility/Equipment Proposals (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Research Proposal (Interdisciplinary Research), 1975,1973 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Research Proposal (Interdisciplinary Research), 1976,1974 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Research Proposal- 2nd year Continuation, Grant DMR 7681083, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Research Proposal- 3rd year Continuation, Grant DMR 768108AO1 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Research Proposal- 3rd year Continuation, Grant DMR 7924008 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Research Proposal- 2nd year Continuation, Grant DMR 7924008, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Research Proposal, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Research Proposal, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Research Proposal- 2nd year Continuation, Grant DMR 8217227, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Research Proposal- 3rd year Continuation, Grant DMR 8217227, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Research Proposal- Acquisition of an Enviornmental Scanning Electron Microscope, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - NSF Proposal Reference, 1991,1996 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Capital Equipment Proposal Files, 1995-1997 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Budget Revisions, Internal Proposals, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Capital Requests- Proposals and Corresp., 1988 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Equipment Request Proposals, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Research Proposal, 1986-1989 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Research Proposal- Applied and ENGG Physics, Silcox Materials Research Laboratory, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Research Proposal- Applied and ENGG Physics, Silcox Materials Research Laboratory, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Research Proposal- Physics, Silsbee Materials Research Laboratory, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Vice President for Research- Proposals, 1994-1997 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Vice President for Research- Proposals, 1989-1994 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Vice President for Research- Proposals, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Vice President for Research- Proposals, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - NSH Grant- DMR 9121654, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Proposal-Simmons, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - KRU SIUS, Peter SRC Ultra-Shallow; ITR, IMR Proposals, 1999-2002 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - IGERT Proposal, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Ashcroft and Eastman- MURI Proposal, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Research Proposal- Acquisition of an Electron Microprobe- Di Salvo, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Proposal to NSF for Postdoc Positions, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Proposal for a Materials Research Science and ENGG Center, Jan 2005 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - NSF Proposal #011877 Info-Small Mechanical Oscillators, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Proposals-Research Exerperience for Teachers, 1999-2001 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Computing Facility Requests Materials Science Center, 1981-1988 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Computer Proposal- Original Figures and Forms, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Intel Proposal- Onyx Computer Acquisition, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - CCMR Capital Equipment Request- L. Derry, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Special Purpose Grants, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Proposal- Standard Oil, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Proposal- Vought Corp., 1984 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Proposal- Argonne National Laboratory, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Capital Equipment Requests, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Capital Equipment Requests, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - MRSEC Prepoposal, References, Reviewer Comments, Suggested Reviewers, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Tanenbaum NSF Career Award, Silcox-Topcon, ROA Proposal, 2000,1998 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - REU NSF Grant Proposals, 1992, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Materials Research- Capital Equipment Proposal Files, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Capital Equipment Requests- Corresp., 1993-1997 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - CCMR-IRG Proposals, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Capital Requests- Corresp., 1982-1985, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - New and Renewed IRG Proposals- Corresp., 1999 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - CCMR Proposal- Review Notebook, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Proposals- Corresp., 1986-1990 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Research Proposal (Silsbee) Materials Research Laboratory, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Research Proposal (Silsbee) Materials Research Laboratory, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Research Proposal Materials Science Center- Silcox Materials Research Laboratory, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Research Proposal (Silcox) Materials Research Laboratory, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Research Proposal (Silcox) 'New Ventures in Biomaterials', 1993 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Research Proposal- Materials Science Center; Silcox- Materials Research and ENGG Center, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Research Proposal- Materials Science Center; Materials Research and ENGG Center, 1996-2001 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Convex Computer Revised Proposal, 1988-1990 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Reponse- Computer Proposal (Original), 1987 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - IBM Workstation Proposal, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - MRL Program Policy Statement Revised Proposal- DMR 8818588, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Equipment Proposal- Acquisition of Advanced Computing Equipment for Experimental Materials Science- Silcox, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Equipment Proposal- Fischer, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Advanced Computing Equipment Proposal, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Computer Proposal- Cirriculum Vitae (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - SEED Proposal- Malliaras and Craighead, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - CMSC Seed Proposals, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - CMSC Request for Additional Funding Form, MSC Reports, 1960's (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Proposal- Simmons- Info, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Proposal- Simmons- Info, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - MSC Research Proposals- Part I, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - MSC Research Proposals- Part II, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Internal Proposals, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - MSC Proposal Budget Requests & Study Groups, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - MSC Proposal Budget Requests & Study Groups, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - MSC Proposal Budget Requests & Study Groups, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Research Proposal- MRSEC- Silcox, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Funding Request 3rd Year Continuation Grant, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Corresp./Proposals- MRL, MSC (misc), 1990-1992 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Proposal- Research Experience for Minorities (Silsbee), 1989 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Proposal- Materials Research Laboratory, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - SEED Projects/Proposals, 2001-2003 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Series IV. Committees
  - Subseries IVa: Executive
    - MSC Members, 1960- 1962 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - MSC Executive Committee Meetings, Jul 1960- Jun 1962 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - MSC Executive Committee Meetings, Jul 1962- Jun 1964 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - MSC Budgets/ Exec. Committee Meeting, 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - MSC Budgets/ Exec. Committee Meeting, 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - MSC Members, 1963-1965 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - MSC Executive Committee Meetings, Jul 1964- Jun 1965 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - MSC Budgets/ Exec. Committee Meeting, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - MSC Budgets/ Exec. Committee Meeting, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1965-1966 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - MSC Members Correspondence, Jul 1965- Jan 1970 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - MSC Executive Committee Meetings, Jul 1966- Jun 1968 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - MSC Budgets/ Exec. Committee Meeting, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Executive Committee Meetings, Jul 1969- Jun 1971 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - MSC Members Correspondence, Jan 1970- Jul 1970 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - MSC Central Facility- Review Committee Reports, MSC Central Facility- Annual Reports, 1970, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Executive Commitee Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Executive Commitee Meetings, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Executive Commitee Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - MSC Executive Commitee Meetings, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Executive Commitee Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - MSC Executive Committee Members- I, Jul 1974- Jun 1976 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - MSC Executive Committee Members- II, Jul 1974- Jun 1976 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Executive Committee Meetings, 1974-1977 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - MSC Executive Committee Meetings- Ballots/Committee Representation, 1974-1977 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - MSC Member Proposal and Support History, 1974-1991 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - MSC Executive Committee Files, Jul 1976- Jun 1978 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Executive Commitee Meetings- I, 1976-1978 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Executive Commitee Meetings-II, 1976-1978 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - MSC Executive Committee Files, Jul 1976- Dec 1979 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - MSC Executive Committee Meetings, Jun 1978- Aug 1980 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Executive Commitee Members, Post 1978 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Executive Committee- Research Expenditures, 1980's (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Executive Commitee Meetings, 1980-1983 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - MSC Members' File, Jan 1980- Jun 1988 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - MSC Executive Committee Meetings, Aug 1980- Apr 1982 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - MSC Executive Committee Meetings, Jul 1982- Jun 1984 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - MSC Executive Commitee Meetings, 1982,1989 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - MSC Executive Commitee Meetings, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee- Research Expenditures, 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - MSC Executive Commitee Meetings, 1987-1992 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Originals for Exec. Comm Meeting, April 1988 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - MSC Executive Committee Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - MSC Members- Correspondence, Memos, Meetings, 1988-1992 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Old Executive Committee Meetings, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - MSC Executive Committee Meetings, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - MSC Executive Committee Meetings, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - MSC Executive Committee Minutes, 1990-1993 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - MSC Executive Committee Meetings, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - MSC Central Facilities Review, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - MSC Executive Committee Files, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - MSC Executive Committee Meetings, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - MSC Executive Committee Files, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - MSC Executive Committee Meetings, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - MSC Members- Correspondence, Memos, Meetings, 1993-1997 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - MSC Executive Committee Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - MSC Executive Commitee Meetings, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Executive Commitee- New Positions I, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Executive Commitee- New Positions II, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Executive Commitee- New Positions, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - MSC Executive Committee Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - MSC Executive Commitee Meetings, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Executive Committee Meetings, Jan 1998- Sept 1998 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Executive Committee Meetings, Oct 1998- Dec 1998 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Excomm Info., 1998 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Executive Committee Meetings, Feb 1999-Jul 1999 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Executive Committee Meetings, Aug 1999- Dec 1999 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Executive Committee Meetings, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Executive Committee Meetings, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Executive Committee Meetings Research Reporting, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Subseries IVb: Visiting
    - Visiting Committee Meeting Records, 1960-1969 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Visiting Committee Nominees and Resignations, 1960-1973 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Visiting Committee Nominees and Resignations, 1960-1974 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Visiting Committee Meeting Reports, 1960-1974 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - General Letters to Visiting Committee, 1962-1974 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - NSF Structure, Personnel, Operations, 1966-1992 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Naval Research Team Visit, 1967-1977 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - US Naval Ordinance Laboratory Visit, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Center and Program Directors' Meetings, 1968-1974 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Sub-Committees Files, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - MRL Directors' Meetings, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - NSF Site Visits and Review Committees, 1971,1979 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - NSF-Proposals and Guidelines, 1971-1983 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - MRL Directors' Meetings, 1975-1977 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Report of Science Application Task Force, Jul 1977 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - MRL Directors' Meetings, 1978-1984 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - NSF Site Visits and Review Committees, 1979-1982 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Dr. Herbert Bennett Visit, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Executive Subcommittee of the DMR Advisory, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - MRL Directors' Policy Committee Correspondence, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Center and Program Directors' Meetings, 1981-1983 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Executive Committee of the NMR/NSF, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - MRL Advisory Committee Discussion Schedule, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Center and Program Directors' Meetings, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - NSF Site Reviews/Study Groups, Nov 1985- Nov 1990 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Past Site Visit Letters & Questionaires, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - NSF Site Review, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Information- NSF Site Visit, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - NSF Site Visit, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - NSF Site Visit, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Center and Program Directors' Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - NSF Site Visit Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - NSF Site Visit, Oct 1988 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - NSF Site Visit, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Dr. Corson Visit, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - MRL Program- Research Highlights, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Center and Program Directors' Meeting, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Materials Research Committee for NSF Reorganization, A. DeGraff Visit, NSF Budget Office Visit, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Center Directors- Meetings, Corresp., 1989 (Box 23, Folder 14)